[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "When you walked into the room and there is the father of this young man who took your daughter's life, what goes through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "walked", "into", "the", "room", "and", "there", "is", "the", "father", "of", "this", "young", "man", "who", "took", "your", "daughter", "'s", "life", ",", "what", "goes", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "One of the reasons I wanted to speak to him, I wanted to speak to him as a father, one father to another father.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "reasons", "I", "wanted", "to", "speak", "to", "him", ",", "I", "wanted", "to", "speak", "to", "him", "as", "a", "father", ",", "one", "father", "to", "another", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "RP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Did you get any kind of insight into what may have been the main trigger here?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "any", "kind", "of", "insight", "into", "what", "may", "have", "been", "the", "main", "trigger", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I don't think there is any one particular theme that spit out more than another.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "is", "any", "one", "particular", "theme", "that", "spit", "out", "more", "than", "another", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Had he been able to work out in his head what had happened to his son?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "he", "been", "able", "to", "work", "out", "in", "his", "head", "what", "had", "happened", "to", "his", "son", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Not particularly, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "particularly", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Do you have it in your heart to forgive Adam Lanza for what he did or is that simply a step too far?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "it", "in", "your", "heart", "to", "forgive", "Adam", "Lanza", "for", "what", "he", "did", "or", "is", "that", "simply", "a", "step", "too", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "It's definitely a kind of a step in this process.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "definitely", "a", "kind", "of", "a", "step", "in", "this", "process", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Without getting into any detail of any of the gun control debate, do you think that particularly the politicians who it seems to many people are making decisions based around protecting their political lives, if you like, over their principle, do you think if any of them had had to go through what you and your family have gone through, what any of the families of Sandy Hook, you think they would make decisions like that in a different way?", "question_tokens": ["Without", "getting", "into", "any", "detail", "of", "any", "of", "the", "gun", "control", "debate", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "particularly", "the", "politicians", "who", "it", "seems", "to", "many", "people", "are", "making", "decisions", "based", "around", "protecting", "their", "political", "lives", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "over", "their", "principle", ",", "do", "you", "think", "if", "any", "of", "them", "had", "had", "to", "go", "through", "what", "you", "and", "your", "family", "have", "gone", "through", ",", "what", "any", "of", "the", "families", "of", "Sandy", "Hook", ",", "you", "think", "they", "would", "make", "decisions", "like", "that", "in", "a", "different", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Speaking from my own experience, which is all I can do, is just say that whenever something happens in your life that you're faced to make that kind of hard decision, and it changes your outlook on the entire world, then it needs to make some kind of a change within you.", "answer_tokens": ["Speaking", "from", "my", "own", "experience", ",", "which", "is", "all", "I", "can", "do", ",", "is", "just", "say", "that", "whenever", "something", "happens", "in", "your", "life", "that", "you", "'re", "faced", "to", "make", "that", "kind", "of", "hard", "decision", ",", "and", "it", "changes", "your", "outlook", "on", "the", "entire", "world", ",", "then", "it", "needs", "to", "make", "some", "kind", "of", "a", "change", "within", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have each other?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "to", "have", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I definitely feel lucky to have her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "definitely", "feel", "lucky", "to", "have", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "EX", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "I mean, do you have a mechanism to cope?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "have", "a", "mechanism", "to", "cope", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "The best thing we have been able to come up with is when you go through something like this and there will be that many emotions, you mentioned a whole list of emotions, all of those can happen to you in a single day or one of those emotions can take over your life for weeks at a time.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "thing", "we", "have", "been", "able", "to", "come", "up", "with", "is", "when", "you", "go", "through", "something", "like", "this", "and", "there", "will", "be", "that", "many", "emotions", ",", "you", "mentioned", "a", "whole", "list", "of", "emotions", ",", "all", "of", "those", "can", "happen", "to", "you", "in", "a", "single", "day", "or", "one", "of", "those", "emotions", "can", "take", "over", "your", "life", "for", "weeks", "at", "a", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Emilie"]}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Is that a sign that you might be able to have some kind of life going forward, that perhaps didn't seem possible a couple months ago?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "sign", "that", "you", "might", "be", "able", "to", "have", "some", "kind", "of", "life", "going", "forward", ",", "that", "perhaps", "did", "n't", "seem", "possible", "a", "couple", "months", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "The morning after Emilie died, I was greeted by my other two daughters, I knew that I had a reason to continue in this life and I knew that they were my reason to get up that morning and to continue to be the best dad that I can be.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "morning", "after", "Emilie", "died", ",", "I", "was", "greeted", "by", "my", "other", "two", "daughters", ",", "I", "knew", "that", "I", "had", "a", "reason", "to", "continue", "in", "this", "life", "and", "I", "knew", "that", "they", "were", "my", "reason", "to", "get", "up", "that", "morning", "and", "to", "continue", "to", "be", "the", "best", "dad", "that", "I", "can", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "What can you say as a father and indeed, Alissa as a mother, to the two little ones about what happened to their big sister?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "say", "as", "a", "father", "and", "indeed", ",", "Alissa", "as", "a", "mother", ",", "to", "the", "two", "little", "ones", "about", "what", "happened", "to", "their", "big", "sister", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I think it's very important to be open about it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "important", "to", "be", "open", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alissa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "What do you want her legacy to be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "her", "legacy", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "ARKER: She embodied so much in her life.", "answer_tokens": ["ARKER", ":", "She", "embodied", "so", "much", "in", "her", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, Piers, in this country, laws have to abide by the constitution of the state that they're enacted in as well as under the federal Constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "in", "this", "country", ",", "laws", "have", "to", "abide", "by", "the", "constitution", "of", "the", "state", "that", "they", "'re", "enacted", "in", "as", "well", "as", "under", "the", "federal", "Constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Or do you?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, I would hope the British folks talk about it as much.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "hope", "the", "British", "folks", "talk", "about", "it", "as", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "If we didn't have the guns, who would you have turned to?", "question_tokens": ["If", "we", "did", "n't", "have", "the", "guns", ",", "who", "would", "you", "have", "turned", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Where was Winston Churchill when all this was going on?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "was", "Winston", "Churchill", "when", "all", "this", "was", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Just say thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "say", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Winston Churchill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "How many existing gun control laws are there in America, do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "existing", "gun", "control", "laws", "are", "there", "in", "America", ",", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I've heard about 20,000.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "heard", "about", "20,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Do you know how many?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Now, Piers --", "answer_tokens": ["Now", ",", "Piers", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Do you know how many?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Here's the point.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January"]}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WP$", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do you know an answer or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "an", "answer", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "-- back in January, if you focus on the gun, you miss the opportunity to zero in on the problem, which is never the gun per se, but always in whose hands are the guns.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "back", "in", "January", ",", "if", "you", "focus", "on", "the", "gun", ",", "you", "miss", "the", "opportunity", "to", "zero", "in", "on", "the", "problem", ",", "which", "is", "never", "the", "gun", "per", "se", ",", "but", "always", "in", "whose", "hands", "are", "the", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Hey, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I want to talk about your body, as I always do when you come in to be interviewed by me, because you look ripped in this movie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "your", "body", ",", "as", "I", "always", "do", "when", "you", "come", "in", "to", "be", "interviewed", "by", "me", ",", "because", "you", "look", "ripped", "in", "this", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "But did you like that story line, of the redemption, this incredibly capable, slightly tormented agent?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "like", "that", "story", "line", ",", "of", "the", "redemption", ",", "this", "incredibly", "capable", ",", "slightly", "tormented", "agent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What was that like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Well, they're amazing individuals.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "amazing", "individuals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "The obvious question is, what on Earth are you two up to?", "question_tokens": ["The", "obvious", "question", "is", ",", "what", "on", "Earth", "are", "you", "two", "up", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "RP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "That is me trying to get a job.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "me", "trying", "to", "get", "a", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "This was actually for charity, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "was", "actually", "for", "charity", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "It was for charity.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "for", "charity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: How do we know we can trust this?", "question_tokens": ["NIDENTIFIED", "MALE", ":", "How", "do", "we", "know", "we", "can", "trust", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Banning is ex-special forces, Ranger battalion.", "answer_tokens": ["Banning", "is", "ex-special", "forces", ",", "Ranger", "battalion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "How are you now all?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "now", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Great.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Great movie.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Did you think it would be good to have more women in the top roles of government?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "it", "would", "be", "good", "to", "have", "more", "women", "in", "the", "top", "roles", "of", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I think absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "It makes it looks like it's manly, it's powerful to have a gun and you may get away with whatever you want to get away with?", "question_tokens": ["It", "makes", "it", "looks", "like", "it", "'s", "manly", ",", "it", "'s", "powerful", "to", "have", "a", "gun", "and", "you", "may", "get", "away", "with", "whatever", "you", "want", "to", "get", "away", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "How do you feel as a parent?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "as", "a", "parent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "He wants to now and I try to hold it at bay.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "wants", "to", "now", "and", "I", "try", "to", "hold", "it", "at", "bay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Where is it?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "You've got to admit, we do.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "to", "admit", ",", "we", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "He's a bit of a heartthrob, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "heartthrob", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Yeah, he is, and a very nice guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "he", "is", ",", "and", "a", "very", "nice", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "A hundred percent.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "hundred", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Are you thinking what I'm thinking?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "thinking", "what", "I", "'m", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I can't think of anybody better.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "think", "of", "anybody", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Would any actor turn that down?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "any", "actor", "turn", "that", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "A billion dollar franchise?", "question_tokens": ["A", "billion", "dollar", "franchise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130322pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "What Scottish accent?", "question_tokens": ["What", "Scottish", "accent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "You've still got a refuge of it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "still", "got", "a", "refuge", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]